Contact

7000572200 (Home) amitpandharikar@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amit-pandharikar-562282127 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Excel
Sql developer
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Languages

Marathi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Professional Working)

Certifications

Digital Marketing
Sololearn SQL
Introduction to Data Science
Programming with Python
Data Analytics and Visualization

Honors-Awards

Robotics workshop

Amit Pandharikar

Intern

Indore

Summary

Experience=1 month Internship done at Xpert.Participated in Virtual Internship of Microsoft at Insidesherpa.com. Civil servant passionate.Legitimate speaker. Computer skills- C , C++, Python, MySql , SQLite ,Oracle sql plus, SQLStudio ,HTML ,CSS , NetBeans , QTdesignerQTdesigner, Tableau software

Experience

Xpert - Learn from the best for FREE Technical Writer Intern June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months) Intern

Microsoft Virtual Internship June 2020 - June 2020 (1 month)

Education

Atomic Energy Central School B.tech, PCM · (2007 - 2019)